[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A coral island, that consists of a coral reef, enclosing a depression in the centre is called this.", "correct_answer": "Atoll", "incorrect_answers": ["Patch", "Lagoon", "There is no common name"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Blazing Saddles, was the ministers Bible shot when he interrupted the Waco Kid?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nutria meat is lean and low in what?", "correct_answer": "Cholesterol", "incorrect_answers": ["Iron", "Sodium", "Fiber"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word means fear of killers?", "correct_answer": "Foniasophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Feretrophobia", "Febriphobia", "Frigophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a genuine mathematical principle?", "correct_answer": "The Pigeon Hole Principle", "incorrect_answers": ["The Inner Calculus Principle", "The Second Integral Theorem", "The Continuum Principle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the Red Baron hunting Beagle from Charles Schultz popular comic strip, Peanuts.", "correct_answer": "Snoopy", "incorrect_answers": ["Scooby", "Lassie", "Odie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lego Group, best known for the manufacture of Lego-brand toys, was founded in 1932 in this country.", "correct_answer": "Denmark", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweden", "Austria", "The Netherlands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you flip a fair coin three times what is the probability you will get three heads ?", "correct_answer": "one out of eight", "incorrect_answers": ["one out of six", "one out of three", "three out of eight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Friday the 13th, just before Steve heads back to the camp he is at a little cafe. What is the name of the waitress that is working there?", "correct_answer": "Sandy", "incorrect_answers": ["Joan", "Mary", "Catherine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the term Triceratops, referring to a dinosaur genus discovered in 1888 in North America?", "correct_answer": "Three horns on the face", "incorrect_answers": ["Three heads", "Beast with three tails", "Three-tongued beast"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor said the line That\u2019s ok, I don\u2019t shop here?", "correct_answer": "Sylvester Stallone in Cobra", "incorrect_answers": ["Nicholas Cage in Raising Arizona", "Bruce Willis in Hudson Hawk", "Warren Beatty in Bonnie and Clyde"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Napoleon\u2019s uncle Rico is constantly contemplating his high school football years and one particular game when the coach failed to put him in the game. What year was that game played?", "correct_answer": "1982", "incorrect_answers": ["1989", "1980", "1979"]}]